<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NavCoin Community Site on NavCoin.org</title>
    <link>https://navcoin.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NavCoin Community Site on NavCoin.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 17:47:48 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://navcoin.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NavCoin Wallets</title>
      <link>https://navcoin.org/downloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 08:09:08 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://navcoin.org/downloads/</guid>
      <description>Choosing a Wallet NavCoin is an open source protocol and NavCoin wallets are maintained by a range of organisations and individuals. It’s advised to take the time to educate yourself about the wallets listed on this page and how to secure your funds. Always remember that it is your responsibility to choose your wallet carefully and adopt good practices in order to protect your money.
 Ask the Community   NavCoin Core Wallet These wallets run the blockchain &amp;amp; participate in validating transactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About This Website</title>
      <link>https://navcoin.org/about-this-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 07:41:22 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://navcoin.org/about-this-website/</guid>
      <description>Who maintains NavCore.org? Navcoin.org is maintained by the NavCore team and other NavCoin Community Members. NavCoin is a community project and we are exploring ways to further decentralise the management of this website and it’s content.
If you have a suggestion, or want to get your project added to the roadmap, talk to a community member on the NavCoin Discord who can help get your update integrated.
 NavCoin Discord   Separating concerns The NavCoin Core Developers are working towards making the navcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become A NavCoin Merchant</title>
      <link>https://navcoin.org/how-to-accept-navcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 07:41:22 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://navcoin.org/how-to-accept-navcoin/</guid>
      <description>How to accept NavCoin Accepting NavCoin in your online shopping cart or retail location is easy and convenient, with options to suit individuals and businesses of any size.  Merchant Tools   random
random
For your store - NavPay NavPay is a light wallet that you can use to accept digital payments in NavCoin on your mobile or desktop. Payments show up almost instantly and your balance is protected because your private keys are stored on your device, not the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribute</title>
      <link>https://navcoin.org/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 07:41:22 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://navcoin.org/contribute/</guid>
      <description>NavCoin Development NavCoin is free software and any developer can contribute to the project. Everything you need is in the GitHub repository. Please make sure to read and follow the development process described in the README, as well as to provide good quality code and respect all guidelines.
 NavCoin GitHub   Beyond NavCoin Core There is a whole eco-system of software which developers have created to operate on or alongside the NavCoin protocol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With NavCoin</title>
      <link>https://navcoin.org/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 07:41:22 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://navcoin.org/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>1. Download the latest version of the wallet This will allow you to send/receive transactions, take ownership of your private keys, and if you use the NavCoin core wallet you can contribute to transaction validation on the network.
 Download Your Wallet    2. Install and set up your wallet Once you have installed the wallet, you should back up your keys and follow the installation process. If you use the NavCoin core wallet, it will take a number of hours to sync and catch up with the blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manifestos</title>
      <link>https://navcoin.org/manifestos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 07:41:22 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://navcoin.org/manifestos/</guid>
      <description>NavCoin Core Manifestos The objective of NavCoin Developer and Content Manifestos is to clearly set out the reasons contributors to the NavCoin community do what we do, how we do it and why. These documents cover guiding principles, purpose, scope of work and operational requirements to ensure we share the same values and always operate in the best interests of the network.
 Download Manifestos   Why decentralized governance is revolutionary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merchants</title>
      <link>https://navcoin.org/merchants/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 07:41:22 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://navcoin.org/merchants/</guid>
      <description>Merchants accepting NavCoin Anyone can accept NavCoin on their website or in their store to receive instant global payments.
If your store accepts NavCoin and you would like to be listed on this page, read about how you can contribute to this website through the link below.  Contribute To This Page   Pay With NavCoin Here You can use your NavCoin to buy all sorts of things online and in stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is NavCoin?</title>
      <link>https://navcoin.org/about-navcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 07:41:22 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://navcoin.org/about-navcoin/</guid>
      <description>Simple but Powerful NavCoin is a decentralized cryptocurrency that uses peer-to-peer technology to operate with no central authority or banks; managing transactions and the issuing of NavCoin is carried out collectively by the network. NavCoin is open-source; its design is public, nobody owns or controls NavCoin and everyone can take part.
NavCoin has a range of sleek and intuitive wallets that allows you to easily manage your NavCoin and keep your funds secure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buying NavCoin</title>
      <link>https://navcoin.org/buying-navcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 07:41:22 +1301</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://navcoin.org/buying-navcoin/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrency Exchanges NavCoin is publicly mined and ran no token sale. The only way to get NAV is to purchase it from a third party or exchange. Exchanges provide highly varying degrees of safety, security, privacy, and control over your funds and information. Perform your own due diligence and choose a wallet where you will keep your NavCoin before selecting an exchange.
        BTC / NAV</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NavCoin Community Site</title>
      <link>https://navcoin.org/_index.es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 17:47:48 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://navcoin.org/_index.es/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://navcoin.org/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 17:47:48 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://navcoin.org/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of our site (https://navcoin.org). We use your personal information to better understand your usage of the site, and to collect traffic statistics.
By using the site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Log Data Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our site (“Log Data”).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use</title>
      <link>https://navcoin.org/terms-of-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 17:47:48 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://navcoin.org/terms-of-use/</guid>
      <description>Terms of Use © NavCoin 2014-2018 is released under the MIT license.
By using the NavCoin softwares or network, you also agree to the following terms of use.
No Investment advice This website does not provide individual or customized legal, tax, financial, or investment services. Since each individual’s situation is unique, a qualified professional should be consulted before making financial decisions. Since NAV is meant to be used as a medium of exchange, nothing on this website constitutes investment advice or a solicitation to buy, hold, invest in, own, or use NAV.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>